question_data = [
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Studio Ghibli is a Japanese animation studio responsible for the films 'Wolf Children' and 'The Boy and the Beast'.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In Kill La Kill, the weapon of the main protagonist is a katana. ",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "The anime 'Lucky Star' follows the story of one girl who is unaware she is God.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Gosho Aoyama Made This Series: (Detective Conan / Case Closed!)",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In the 'Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya' series, the narrator goes by the nickname Kyon.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In Pokemon, Ash's Pikachu refuses to go into a pokeball.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In the ';Toaru Kagaku no Railgun anime,  espers can only reach a maximum of level 6 in their abilities.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "The name of the attack 'Kamehameha' in Dragon Ball Z was named after a famous king of Hawaii.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Kiznaiver is an adaptation of a manga.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In Chobits, Hideki found Chii in his apartment.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    }
]